{
    "subject": "resource/Ray_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/budget",
    "object": "4.0E7",
    "human_readable": "The budget of Ray (film) is $40,000,000.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7889997363090515,
            "question": "What was the budget for the film Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6787249445915222,
            "question": "What is the estimated cost of producing the film Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6444103717803955,
            "question": "How much money was spent making the movie Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.512352466583252,
            "question": "Could the budget for Ray be considered significant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102897882461548,
            "question": "Do you think the budget of Ray contributed to the quality of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4217757284641266,
            "question": "What factors might have influenced the budget of Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4186674952507019,
            "question": "What could have been achieved with a larger budget for Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40577203035354614,
            "question": "How does the budget of Ray compare to other films in a similar genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3662104904651642,
            "question": "Was Ray a high-budget production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34881630539894104,
            "question": "What is the significance of a large budget in filmmaking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The budget of Ray (film) is $40,000,000.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2662_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ray a high-budget production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2662_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the budget of Ray compare to other films in a similar genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2662_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What could have been achieved with a larger budget for Ray?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2662_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2662_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate the triple \"The budget of Batman Begins is $150 million\", I will analyze the context information provided.\n\nHere's the result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The text mentions that Nolan's 2005 feature Batman Begins has a budget of \"$150 million\", however it is mentioned as \"tails closely behind Oppenheimer with a budget of $150 million\". It implies that there are other movies that have a higher budget than Batman Begins, including Oppenheimer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information about the budget of the film \"Ray\" or any related financial details. Therefore, the statement cannot be verified with the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}